<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-19T01:34:56+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">The Importance Of Travel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Importance Of Travel" /><published>2020-06-06T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-06-06T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-travel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel">&lt;p&gt;Maybe you seek to become more compassionate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To take better care of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or, to find a greater purpose?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re all on our own unique journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though some are more conscious of it than others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if you’ve ever left home for an extended period of time, you know that an external journey can aid the internal one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How - upon returning - you view everything with a fresh pair of eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticing new opportunities, and how previous seemingly insurmountable problems are no longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what to do and how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything’s clear and your mind more open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay in the same place for too long and you get stuck in a rut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of this wisdom lives on in our modern culture - but on a very low level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know that we’re supposed to travel - but why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do we know?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not really.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s relaxing - or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be totally honest, we mostly do it because everyone else does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once a year we partake in the standard routine of lying down on a beach at a fancy hotel. And why complain? It’s pleasurable!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, these kinds of vacations seldom leave a mark on us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They tend to melt together into one foggy pot of sandy feet and margaritas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again, we’re reminded that pleasure is not a satisfactory goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travel can be so much more than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A challenging hike through the mountains might make you realize how beautifully meaningful life is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A month of sailing alone could bring you closer to your friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And a solo retreat into the woods might make you religious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travel and you shall progress.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gustaf Broman</name></author><summary type="html">Maybe you seek to become more compassionate.</summary></entry></feed>